import React, { useState } from "react";
import EDU from "../component/eduCard";
import WORK from "../component/workCard";

function ResumeComponent() {
  const [studie, setStudierna] = useState([
    {
      question: "FrontEnd Development | Noroff, Oslo  |  2018-2020",
      answer: "Currently studying FrontEnd Development at Noroff.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Computer Technology | NTI | 2014-2016",
      answer: "Online course in Computer Technology at NTI.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Computer Coordination and Support | NTI | 2014-2016",
      answer: "Online course in Computer Coordination and Support at NTI.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Network Technology | NTI | 2014-2016",
      answer: "Network Technology. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Administration Of Network and Server Equipment | NTI | 2014-2016",
      answer:
        "Online course in Administration Of Network and Server Equipment at NTI.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Network Administration | NTI | 2014-2016",
      answer: "Online course in Network Administration at NTI.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Social Science and Economics | Klara Gymnasium, Linköping  |  2008-2011",
      answer: " 3 year highschool education",
      open: false,
    },
  ]);

  const toggleEDU = (index) => {
    setStudierna(
      studie.map((studier, i) => {
        if (i === index) {
          studier.open = !studier.open;
        } else {
          studier.open = false;
        }
        return studier;
      })
    );
  };

  const [jobb, setJobben] = useState([
    {
      question: "IT technician | Subway  Norge  |  2019-Present",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Kitchen Chief | Jensens Böfhus | 2017-Present",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Warehouse Employee | Coca Cola | 2015-2016",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Warehouse Employee | Coop | 2013-2014",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Warehouse Employee  | Tine Meijeri | 2012-2013",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan.",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Salesman | Fjordkraft | 2011",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
    {
      question: "Postman | Posten |  2010-2011",
      answer:
        "Lucas ipsum dolor sit amet chommell ithorian biggs sullustan desann anakin tambor saché b4-d4 kasan. ",
      open: false,
    },
  ]);

  const toggleWORK = (index) => {
    setJobben(
      jobb.map((jobben, i) => {
        if (i === index) {
          jobben.open = !jobben.open;
        } else {
          jobben.open = false;
        }
        return jobben;
      })
    );
  };

  return (
    <div className="container container-resume">
      <div className="col-sm-12 profil">
        <h1 className="info-text about">About Me</h1>
        <hr></hr>

        <p className="about-text">
          {" "}
          My Name is Arvid. I've lived in Oslo for the last 10 years but I'm
          originally from Sweden. I work as a kitchen chief. Currently studying
          FrontEnd Development. Likes design
        </p>
        <img
          className="resume-img"
          src={require("./../images/me.svg")}
          alt="img"
        />
      </div>
      <hr className="hr-edu"></hr>
      <h1 className="info-text-edu">Education</h1>
      <h1 className="info-text-work">Work Experience</h1>

      <div className="work-edu-container">
        <div className="col-sm-6 utbildning">
          <div className="studie">
            {studie.map((studier, i) => (
              <EDU index={i} studier={studier} toggleEDU={toggleEDU} />
            ))}
          </div>
        </div>
        <div className="col-sm-6 work-exp">
          <div className="jobb">
            {jobb.map((jobben, i) => (
              <WORK index={i} jobben={jobben} toggleWORK={toggleWORK} />
            ))}
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  );
}

export default ResumeComponent;

hr {
  height: 20px;
  background-color: $bg-colour;
  border: none;
}
.hr-edu {
  margin-top: 200px;
}
.container .resume-row{
  background-color: white;
  padding: 0;
}

.utblidning {
  text-align: center;
  display: inline-block;
}


.profil {
  height: 200px;
  width: 100%;
  margin-bottom: 100px;
}

.resume-img {
  width: 200px;
  position: relative;
  top: -200px;
  left: -400px;
  border-radius: 50%;
}
.info-text {
  position: relative;
  top: 50px;
  left: -60px;
  height: 40px;
  width: 300px;
  font-size: 2em;
  background-color: white;
  color: $text-colour;
  font-family: $text-font;
}

.about {
  margin-left: 100px;
  padding-top: 20px;
}
.about-text {
  padding-top: 0px;
  padding-bottom: 50px;
  font-family: $text-font;
  font-size: 1.5em;
  margin-top: 100px;
  margin-left: 450px;
  margin-right: 100px;
  text-align: center;
}

.info-text-work {
  background-color: white;
  color: $text-colour;
  font-family: $text-font;
  width: 300px;
  position: relative;
  top: -120px;
  left: 700px;
}
.info-text-edu {
  width: 300px;
  position: relative;
  left: 120px;
  top: -60px;
  background-color: white;
  color: $text-colour;
  font-family: $text-font;
}

/*  mobile */

@media (max-width: 600px) {
  .about {
    margin-top: 100px;
  }
  .about-text {
    text-align: center;
    margin-left: 0px;
    margin-right: 0px;
    padding-bottom: 50px;
  }
  .skola {
    margin-left: -100px;
  }
  .info-text-edu {
    text-align: center;
    margin-top: 100px;
    margin-left: -100px;
  }
  .info-text-work {
    position: relative;
    left: 30px;
    top: 500px;
  }
  .jobb {
    margin: 40px;
  }
  .resume-img {
    margin-top: 40px;
    position: absolute;
    left: 25%;
    top: 50px;
  }

  .work-edu-container{
    display: inline-block;
  }
}
